<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>STEMHub Foundation | Empowerment Through STEM Education Blog</title>
        <link>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog</link>
        <description>The best place to stay up-to-date with the latest STEMHub Foundation | Empowerment Through STEM Education news and events.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <image>
            <title>STEMHub Foundation | Empowerment Through STEM Education Blog</title>
            <url>https://stemhubfoundation.com//img/logo_cropped.png</url>
            <link>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2018 STEMHub Foundation</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How To Protect Your Privacy Online While Building Your Brand]]></title>
            <link>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog/2018/05/16/online-privacy.html</link>
            <guid>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog/2018/05/16/online-privacy.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>With data breaches and online stalkers, it’s understandable you might want to be untraceable online. However, if you’re trying to build your brand, you can’t skip having some information about yourself online especially on social media. Why? If no one knows who you are they can’t trust you and won’t listen to you. Consequently, you need to consider relaxing your need for privacy on social media if you want to build a successful brand.</p>
<p>Since the first thing most people do when they hear about someone is to look them up on Google, having a public social media profile is non-negotiable. While people looking you up may sound creepy, most of them mean no harm. They just want to be sure you’re a real person before they warm up to you. And If you don’t have a website, they can’t find out much if your social media profile is private.</p>
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[9 Things You Must Avoid When Networking Online]]></title>
            <link>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog/2018/05/04/networking-online.html</link>
            <guid>https://stemhubfoundation.com//blog/2018/05/04/networking-online.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Asides from free drinks, online networking is a great way to build relationships and open doors that would have been otherwise locked. However, many people whine about how online networking is time wasting. If you belong to this group of whiners, you may have been doing some things wrong. To improve your online networking game, here are 9 things to avoid.</p>
<ol>
<li>Don’t Spam: If you often spam your contacts with irrelevant messages, your contacts may not take you seriously and overlook your important messages. It’s also a great way to get blacklisted. So, send only relevant messages and keep happy new month and “hello, I’m just checking on you” messages to your family and friends.</li>
<li>Mind Your Topic Of Discussion: When you send emails to professional acquaintances, avoid void vagueness &amp; religious undertone (e.g. God bless you). It can send a wrong signal. Go straight to the point. ‬</li>
</ol>
]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>